<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Unofficial Rising Constellation FAQ – Unofficial FAQ</title>
    <link>/Rising-Constellation-FAQ/docs/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Unofficial FAQ on Unofficial Rising Constellation FAQ</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    
	  <atom:link href="/Rising-Constellation-FAQ/docs/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
      
        
      
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Docs: Winning the Game</title>
      <link>/Rising-Constellation-FAQ/docs/concepts/victory/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/Rising-Constellation-FAQ/docs/concepts/victory/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        &lt;h3 id=&#34;victory&#34;&gt;Victory&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;how-does-one-team-win&#34;&gt;How does one team win?&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There are 3 paths to victory. Each path gives 2/3/5 stars depending on the goals reached. The goal of the game is to hit the 12 stars mark first as a team.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;path-of-conquest&#34;&gt;Path of Conquest&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Stars are earned by a faction controlling a sector. Each sector is worth a certain number of Sector Points, and there are thresholds for how many sector points are needed for each of the star levels. You can hover over a sector to see the number of points it is worth (in the middle diamond).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Example progression from a legacy game with 2 factions: &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;table&gt;
&lt;thead&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;th&gt;Stars&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th&gt;Sector Points&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/thead&gt;
&lt;tbody&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;2&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;9&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;3&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;21&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;5&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;32&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;These numbers will be different depending on the map layout and number of factions involved.&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;path-of-influence&#34;&gt;Path of Influence&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Stars are earned by have large populations in star systems. Each system is worth a certain number of Star System Points which is dependant on the population of the system.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h5 id=&#34;star-system-points-per-population&#34;&gt;Star System Points per population&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;table&gt;
&lt;thead&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;th&gt;Population&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th&gt;Star System Points&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/thead&gt;
&lt;tbody&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;&amp;gt;0&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;1&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;&amp;gt;40&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;2&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;&amp;gt;60&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;4&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;&amp;gt;70&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;7&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;&amp;gt;80&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;11&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;&amp;gt;90&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;16&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;&amp;gt;120&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;25&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;&amp;gt;180&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;75&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Example from a Legacy game with 2 factions, and 49 players on one of the factions:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;table&gt;
&lt;thead&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;th&gt;Stars&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th&gt;Sector Points&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/thead&gt;
&lt;tbody&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;2&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;1021&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;3&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;2042&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;5&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;4083&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;These numbers will depend on the number of players in the faction.&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;path-of-shadows&#34;&gt;Path of Shadows&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Stars are earned by Visibility Points which are the first 5 points of visibility on enemy systems. This can be done by an Erased agent using the &lt;a href=&#34;/Rising-Constellation-FAQ/docs/agents/erased/#infiltration&#34;&gt;Infiltration&lt;/a&gt; action. There are thresholds for how many Visibility Points are needed for each of the star levels, and scales by the number of enemy systems.
Unlike the other two paths, this value is hidden from the enemy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Example from a Legacy game with 2 factions mid way into the game:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;table&gt;
&lt;thead&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;th&gt;Stars&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th&gt;Visibility Points&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/thead&gt;
&lt;tbody&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;2&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;415&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;3&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;669&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;5&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;752&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;

      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Docs: Fleet Combat</title>
      <link>/Rising-Constellation-FAQ/docs/concepts/combat/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/Rising-Constellation-FAQ/docs/concepts/combat/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        &lt;h3 id=&#34;how-is-combat-initiated&#34;&gt;How is combat initiated?&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When two &lt;a href=&#34;/Rising-Constellation-FAQ/docs/agents/navarch/&#34;&gt;Navarch&lt;/a&gt; agents are in the same system combat can begin in one of three ways:
#1 A player clicks on the the enemy Navarch while selecting their, and chooses to fight.
#2 A Navarch set to &lt;a href=&#34;/Rising-Constellation-FAQ/docs/agents/navarch/#stance&#34;&gt;Aggressive or Fury stance&lt;/a&gt; will immediately attack enemy fleets in their system.
#3 A Navarch set to &lt;a href=&#34;/Rising-Constellation-FAQ/docs/agents/navarch/#defender&#34;&gt;Defender stance&lt;/a&gt; will begin a fight if the system they are in is under attack (Pillage/Bombard/Colonization)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;how-does-combat-get-resolved&#34;&gt;How does Combat get resolved?&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Combat occurs in rounds during each round the following phases take place:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;1-deployment&#34;&gt;1. Deployment&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The units in the row corresponding to the round number are added to the battlefield.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Example&lt;/strong&gt;: On the first round of combat, the units in the L1 column would be deployed, (Drone Carriers in this case)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;/Rising-Constellation-FAQ/images/fleet_example_1.PNG&#34; alt=&#34;Fleet Example 1&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;2-roll-for-initiative&#34;&gt;2. Roll for initiative&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The two sides compare their morale scores and the units are ordered according to their morale (the highest morale starts)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;3-attack&#34;&gt;3. Attack&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Each unit takes turns making all of its attacks against a random enemy unit on the battlefield.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Example&lt;/strong&gt;: a unit of 2 Gunner ships would make 2 explosive attacks, where a unit of 8 Light Fighters would make 8 * (2 energy attacks + 1 explosive attack) for a total of 24 individual attacks.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;All of the damage from an attack goes to an individual ship, so even if a Gunner attacks and hits a light fighter with 25 health, most of the 390 of its attack is wasted, as it only removes a single ship from the unit of light fighters. &lt;a href=&#34;/Rising-Constellation-FAQ/docs/ships/stats/&#34;&gt;Ship Stats&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;morale&#34;&gt;Morale&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Each ship has a morale base, increased by the level of the navarch of the fleet and the level of the ship.
Ships start at 20 morale, and every level after gets you 0.5% more that also applies to all of the other statistics of the ship
During a fight, if a unit&amp;rsquo;s morale hits 0, they will flee the combat. 
Morale resets at the end of each combat, so units are always back at full morale value before the next fight.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;what-causes-ships-to-no-longer-respond-to-orders-and-flee-in-combat&#34;&gt;What causes ships to no longer respond to orders and flee in combat?&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Running out of morale, which is lost when: other individual ships in the fleet are destroyed, loss of full units, and damage taken.&lt;/p&gt;

      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Docs: Fleet Composition</title>
      <link>/Rising-Constellation-FAQ/docs/strategies/fleets/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/Rising-Constellation-FAQ/docs/strategies/fleets/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        &lt;h3 id=&#34;what-ships-counter-what&#34;&gt;What ships counter what?&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There is still a lot of room to develop new fleet strategies and counters, but some basics about which ships counter other ships can be derived from looking at their stats, and how the fighting mechanics work out:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img style=&#34;background:black&#34; src=&#34;/Rising-Constellation-FAQ/images/svg/ships/interceptor.svg&#34;/&gt;
 &lt;strong&gt;Interceptors&lt;/strong&gt;:
With their high ship count and moderate overall damage, they are a good counter to Gunners, who can only fire once per attack.
&lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img style=&#34;background:black&#34; src=&#34;/Rising-Constellation-FAQ/images/svg/ships/gunner.svg&#34;/&gt;
 &lt;strong&gt;Gunners&lt;/strong&gt;:
With their high explosive damage they do well against high shield targets with low Flack, such as Drone Carriers and Assault Frigates
&lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img style=&#34;background:black&#34; src=&#34;/Rising-Constellation-FAQ/images/svg/ships/drone_carrier.svg&#34;/&gt;
 &lt;strong&gt;Drone Carriers&lt;/strong&gt;:
With their high HP and multiple shots, they are good at taking out fighters of all types.
&lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Corvettes lay somewhere in the middle, 2x or 4x corvettes will have a hard time against any frigate class, but the more combat focused types (Light Corvettes and multi turret) will do well when they hit the 8x level, at least until the frigates hit their 4x. They can however be an early counter to fighter fleets.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When looking to counter a specific enemy fleet, consider setting up a &lt;a href=&#34;https://rising-constellation.com/portal/fight-simulator&#34;&gt;simulated fight&lt;/a&gt; and playing around with your fleet design in terms of order/layout and composition&lt;/p&gt;

      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Docs: Legacy Openers</title>
      <link>/Rising-Constellation-FAQ/docs/strategies/legacy-start/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/Rising-Constellation-FAQ/docs/strategies/legacy-start/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        &lt;h3 id=&#34;legacy&#34;&gt;Legacy&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There are many possible strategies, especially when coordinating with other members in your faction.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The one below is a solid recommendation which could be tweaked, but should provide you with a general idea of where to start.
Credit: &lt;strong&gt;Cookies&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;opening&#34;&gt;Opening&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In most circumstances, you want to colonize 3 systems as soon as possible.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the beginning, build &lt;em&gt;Delta Polytech&lt;/em&gt;&lt;img style=&#34;background:black&#34; src=&#34;/Rising-Constellation-FAQ/images/svg/buildings/university.svg&#34;/&gt;
 on your first planet, buy tech for &lt;em&gt;Citadel&lt;/em&gt; &lt;img style=&#34;background:black&#34; src=&#34;/Rising-Constellation-FAQ/images/svg/buildings/ideo.svg&#34;/&gt;
 and build the &lt;em&gt;Citadel&lt;/em&gt; on the planet as well.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Buy the first technology in habitable, sterile, and asteroid. Build &lt;em&gt;Megapolis&lt;/em&gt;&lt;img style=&#34;background:black&#34; src=&#34;/Rising-Constellation-FAQ/images/svg/buildings/main_building.svg&#34;/&gt;
 on the other habitable and &lt;em&gt;Central Hub&lt;/em&gt; &lt;img style=&#34;background:black&#34; src=&#34;/Rising-Constellation-FAQ/images/svg/buildings/main_building.svg&#34;/&gt;
on the sterile.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Build both &lt;em&gt;Delta Polytech&lt;/em&gt; and &lt;em&gt;Citadel&lt;/em&gt; on the second habitable, and build 3 &lt;em&gt;Residential Districts&lt;/em&gt; &lt;img style=&#34;background:black&#34; src=&#34;/Rising-Constellation-FAQ/images/svg/buildings/house.svg&#34;/&gt;
 on the first habitable for faster population growth.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Build &lt;em&gt;Impact Research Center&lt;/em&gt; &lt;img style=&#34;background:black&#34; src=&#34;/Rising-Constellation-FAQ/images/svg/buildings/microscope.svg&#34;/&gt;
 on the sterile planet, and build one &lt;em&gt;Refining Duct&lt;/em&gt; &lt;img style=&#34;background:black&#34; src=&#34;/Rising-Constellation-FAQ/images/svg/buildings/factory.svg&#34;/&gt;
  on each of the 5 industry potential asteroid.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Wait for &lt;em&gt;Exobiology&lt;/em&gt; patent, and build &lt;em&gt;Experiment stations&lt;/em&gt; &lt;img style=&#34;background:black&#34; src=&#34;/Rising-Constellation-FAQ/images/svg/buildings/microscope.svg&#34;/&gt;
 on every asteroid except the 1 potential one. Buy patent for asteroid level 2, and upgrade asteroid buildings.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Wait for colony ship technology. Buy navarch and colony ship. Look for systems with many habitable slots and good appeal potential because the second system should focus on credit.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Research &lt;em&gt;Publicity Terminal&lt;/em&gt; patent and replace the houses on home planet with &lt;em&gt;Archipelagoes&lt;/em&gt; &lt;img style=&#34;background:black&#34; src=&#34;/Rising-Constellation-FAQ/images/svg/buildings/double_house.svg&#34;/&gt;
 . Research habitable level 2. When colonization is complete, develop the second colony and recall the navarch.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Deploy the navarch in home system once the cooldown finishes, and build the next colony ship. You should get enough ideology for the third system when the second colony ship is completed and moves to its destination.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For Lex, rush &lt;em&gt;Mass Media&lt;/em&gt; and ignore everything else. Buy Lex slots to make sure all lexes are applied. After &lt;em&gt;Mass Media&lt;/em&gt; buy &lt;em&gt;Propaganda&lt;/em&gt; to keep population growing. After that save up for &lt;em&gt;Proto Empire&lt;/em&gt; and after that &lt;em&gt;Extended Administration&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Docs: Navarch</title>
      <link>/Rising-Constellation-FAQ/docs/agents/navarch/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/Rising-Constellation-FAQ/docs/agents/navarch/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        &lt;h2 id=&#34;abilities&#34;&gt;Abilities&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;pillaging-bombingimagesbombingpng&#34;&gt;Pillaging &lt;img src=&#34;/Rising-Constellation-FAQ/images/bombing.PNG&#34; alt=&#34;Bombing&#34;&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Allows a navarch to raid resources from an enemy controlled system or dominion. Compares the navarch&amp;rsquo;s total bombing power against the defense of the system. Increased by Conquest skill, and by having certain types of ships in the fleet. see &lt;a href=&#34;/Rising-Constellation-FAQ/docs/ships/stats/#what-are-the-base-stats-of-all-of-the-ships&#34;&gt;Ship Stats - Bombing&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;does-the-time-to-pillage-depend-on-bombing-power&#34;&gt;Does the time to pillage depend on bombing power?&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;yes slightly depends on defense and bombing power. The base time length for a pillage is 1h&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;how-much-will-i-get-from-pillaging&#34;&gt;How much will I get from pillaging?&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;One pillage gives 150 ticks of the production of the system for a normal level of success, and 200 ticks for a critical. Each pillage lowers % of resources raided by 45% and it recovers over time by .25% per tick&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;conquest-invasionimagesinvasionpng&#34;&gt;Conquest &lt;img src=&#34;/Rising-Constellation-FAQ/images/invasion.PNG&#34; alt=&#34;Invasion&#34;&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Allows a navarch to convert an enemy controlled system or dominion into a system directly under your control. Compares the navarch&amp;rsquo;s total invasion power against the defense of the system. Increased by Conquest skill, and by having certain types of ships in the fleet. see &lt;a href=&#34;/Rising-Constellation-FAQ/docs/ships/stats/#what-are-the-base-stats-of-all-of-the-ships&#34;&gt;Ship Stats - Invasion&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;does-the-time-to-conquest-depend-on-invasion-power&#34;&gt;Does the time to conquest depend on invasion power?&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;yes slightly depends on defense and invasion power&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;how-much-invasion-power-do-i-need&#34;&gt;How much invasion power do I need?&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Invasion power is compared to system defense&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;repair-repairimagesrepairpng&#34;&gt;Repair &lt;img src=&#34;/Rising-Constellation-FAQ/images/repair.PNG&#34; alt=&#34;Repair&#34;&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Repairs the fleet under the navarch&amp;rsquo;s control. Increased by the Leadership skill, and by having certain types of ships in the fleet. see &lt;a href=&#34;/Rising-Constellation-FAQ/docs/ships/stats/#what-are-the-base-stats-of-all-of-the-ships&#34;&gt;Ship Stats - Repair&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;how-long-do-repairs-take&#34;&gt;How long do repairs take?&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Repairs will only happen while a fleet is not moving or engaging in an offensive action. Ships will be repaired starting with the ship at lowest % health first. The rate of repair is:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Repair Score * .5 HP per tick.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Example&lt;/strong&gt;: A navarch with 2 ranks of repair, and has a drone carrier x2 in their fleet will have 
(2 ranks * 4) + (4 score from fleet) = 12 repair score. Repairing 6 HP per tick. So in legacy with 3 minute ticks you can estimate it at 120 HP per hour.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;stance&#34;&gt;Stance&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;defender&#34;&gt;Defender&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Will join into fights, and engage enemies to prevent pillaging/bombarding/colonization. But will not otherwise start a fight with enemies in the same system&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;deserter&#34;&gt;Deserter&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Attempts to flee combat as soon as possible&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;prudent&#34;&gt;Prudent&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Will only fight if directly attacked&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;aggressive&#34;&gt;Aggressive&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Will automatically engage any enemy in the same system&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;fury&#34;&gt;Fury&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Will automatically engage any enemy in the same system
In a future implementation, will also engage non-allied fleets.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;what-happens-if-you-recall-a-navarch-with-a-fleet&#34;&gt;What happens if you recall a Navarch with a fleet?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;recalling them will destroy the fleet&lt;/p&gt;

      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Docs: Stats</title>
      <link>/Rising-Constellation-FAQ/docs/ships/stats/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/Rising-Constellation-FAQ/docs/ships/stats/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        &lt;!-- (&#34;.*\d+)\|(\d+.*&#34;) 
$1\|$2
--&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;what-do-the-stats-mean&#34;&gt;What do the stats mean?&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;shield&#34;&gt;Shield&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Absorbs a percent of incoming energy attacks&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;flack&#34;&gt;Flack&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Chance to fully avoid the incoming explosive attack&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;what-are-the-base-stats-of-all-of-the-ships&#34;&gt;What are the base stats of all of the ships?&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;table&gt;
&lt;thead&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;th&gt;Name&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th&gt;Class&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th&gt;Credit Cost&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th&gt;Tech Cost&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th&gt;Production&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th&gt;Maintenance&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th&gt;Hull&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th&gt;Maneuverability&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th&gt;Shield&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th&gt;Flack&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th&gt;Energy Attack&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th&gt;Explosive Attack&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th&gt;Repair&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th&gt;Invasion&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th&gt;Bombing&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/thead&gt;
&lt;tbody&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;2 Scouts&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;fighter&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;900&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;0&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;120&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;1&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;12&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;90&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;0&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;0&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;[4]&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;[]&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;0&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;0&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;0&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;4 Scouts&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;fighter&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;1800&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;0&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;232&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;2&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;12&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;90&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;0&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;0&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;[4]&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;[]&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;0&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;0&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;0&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;8 Scouts&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;fighter&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;2900&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;0&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;472&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;4&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;12&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;90&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;0&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;0&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;[4]&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;[]&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;0&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;0&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;0&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;16 Scouts&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;fighter&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;5800&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;0&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;944&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;8&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;12&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;90&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;0&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;0&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;[4]&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;[]&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;0&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;0&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;0&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;2 Light Fighters&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;fighter&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;1400&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;0&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;352&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;8&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;25&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;65&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;10&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;0&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;[9|9]&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;[3]&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;0&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;0&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;0&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;4 Light Fighters&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;fighter&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;2700&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;25&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;704&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;16&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;25&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;65&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;10&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;0&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;[9|9]&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;[3]&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;0&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;0&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;0&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;8 Light Fighters&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;fighter&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;4300&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;50&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;1408&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;32&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;25&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;65&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;10&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;0&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;[9|9]&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;[3]&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;0&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;0&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;0&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;16 Light Fighters&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;fighter&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;8600&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;100&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;2824&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;64&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;25&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;65&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;10&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;0&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;[9|9]&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;[3]&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;0&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;0&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;0&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;2 Figheter-Bombers&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;fighter&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;1400&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;0&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;352&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;10&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;20&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;60&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;0&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;0&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;[]&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;[10]&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;0&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;0&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;1&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;4 Figheter-Bombers&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;fighter&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;2700&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;25&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;704&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;20&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;20&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;60&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;0&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;0&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;[]&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;[10]&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;0&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;0&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;1&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;8 Figheter-Bombers&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;fighter&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;4300&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;50&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;1408&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;40&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;20&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;60&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;0&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;0&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;[]&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;[10]&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;0&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;0&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;1&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;16 Figheter-Bombers&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;fighter&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;8600&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;100&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;2824&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;80&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;20&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;60&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;0&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;0&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;[]&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;[10]&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;0&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;0&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;1&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;2 Interceptors&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;fighter&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;1400&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;0&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;352&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;8&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;25&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;75&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;0&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;0&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;[6|6|6|6]&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;[]&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;0&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;0&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;0&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;4 Interceptors&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;fighter&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;2700&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;25&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;704&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;16&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;25&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;75&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;0&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;0&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;[6|6|6|6]&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;[]&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;0&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;0&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;0&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;8 Interceptors&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;fighter&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;4300&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;50&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;1408&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;32&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;25&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;75&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;0&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;0&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;[6|6|6|6]&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;[]&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;0&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;0&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;0&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;16 Interceptors&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;fighter&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;8600&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;100&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;2824&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;64&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;25&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;75&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;0&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;0&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;[6|6|6|6]&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;[]&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;0&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;0&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;0&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;2 Light Corvettes&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;corvette&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;4300&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;80&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;1176&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;14&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;75&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;40&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;30&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;0&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;[19|19]&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;[12]&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;0&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;0&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;2&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;4 Light Corvettes&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;corvette&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;8600&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;160&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;2352&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;28&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;75&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;40&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;30&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;0&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;[19|19]&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;[12]&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;0&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;0&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;2&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;8 Light Corvettes&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;corvette&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;17300&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;320&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;4704&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;56&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;75&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;40&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;30&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;0&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;[19|19]&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;[12]&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;0&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;0&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;2&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;2 Heavy Corvettes&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;corvette&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;4300&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;100&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;1176&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;15&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;110&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;30&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;20&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;15&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;[]&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;[18]&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;0&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;0&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;3&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;4 Heavy Corvettes&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;corvette&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;8600&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;200&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;2352&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;30&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;110&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;30&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;20&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;15&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;[]&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;[18]&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;0&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;0&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;3&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;8 Heavy Corvettes&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;corvette&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;17300&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;400&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;4704&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;60&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;110&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;30&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;20&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;15&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;[]&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;[18]&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;0&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;0&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;3&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;2 Multi-Turret Corvettes&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;corvette&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;8600&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;875&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;1426&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;30&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;335&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;20&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;10&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;7&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;[11|11|11|11|11|11]&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;[]&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;0&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;0&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;0&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;4 Multi-Turret Corvettes&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;corvette&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;17300&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;1750&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;2852&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;60&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;335&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;20&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;10&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;7&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;[11|11|11|11|11|11]&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;[]&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;0&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;0&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;0&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;8 Multi-Turret Corvettes&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;corvette&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;34600&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;3500&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;5704&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;120&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;335&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;20&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;10&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;7&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;[11|11|11|11|11|11]&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;[]&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;0&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;0&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;0&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Colonisation Ship&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;transport&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;80000&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;3000&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;32000&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;100&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;400&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;0&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;10&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;10&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;[]&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;[]&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;0&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;0&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;0&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Carrier&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;transport&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;18000&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;3000&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;6720&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;300&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;800&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;30&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;50&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;5&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;[3|3]&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;[]&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;5&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;25&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;0&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;2 Assault Frigates&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;frigate&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;9200&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;200&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;3920&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;40&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;200&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;20&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;60&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;10&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;[26|26]&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;[77]&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;0&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;2&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;0&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;4 Assault Frigates&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;frigate&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;22000&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;400&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;7840&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;80&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;200&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;20&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;60&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;10&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;[26|26]&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;[77]&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;0&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;2&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;0&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;2 Gunners&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;frigate&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;21600&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;3000&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;3920&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;60&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;320&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;10&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;40&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;25&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;[]&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;[390]&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;0&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;8&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;4 Gunners&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;frigate&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;43200&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;6000&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;7840&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;120&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;320&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;10&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;40&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;25&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;[]&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;[390]&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;0&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;8&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;2 Drone Carriers&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;frigate&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;21600&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;2500&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;5880&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;100&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;950&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;20&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;65&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;30&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;[8|8|8|8|8|8|8|8|8|8]&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;[]&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;2&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;0&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;2&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;4 Drone Carriers&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;frigate&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;43200&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;5000&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;11760&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;200&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;950&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;20&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;65&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;30&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;[8|8|8|8|8|8|8|8|8|8]&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;[]&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;2&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;0&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;2&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;2 Repair Platforms&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;frigate&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;21600&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;2000&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;7840&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;100&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;1400&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;15&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;70&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;40&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;[]&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;[16]&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;30&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;1&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;0&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;4 Repair Platforms&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;frigate&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;43200&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;4000&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;15680&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;200&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;1400&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;15&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;70&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;40&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;[]&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;[16]&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;30&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;1&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;0&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Destroyer&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;capital&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;103200&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;6000&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;16240&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;400&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;4000&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;0&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;65&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;40&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;[60|60|60|60]&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;[45|45|45|100]&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;15&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;10&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;5&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Cruiser&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;capital&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;128000&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;8000&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;19880&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;500&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;5000&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;0&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;50&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;70&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;[70|70]&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;[330]&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;15&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;15&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;40&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Coordinator&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;capital&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;166800&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;10000&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;17456&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;600&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;6000&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;0&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;85&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;75&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;[]&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;[20|20|20]&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;40&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;30&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;0&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;

      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Docs: Siderian</title>
      <link>/Rising-Constellation-FAQ/docs/agents/siderian/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/Rising-Constellation-FAQ/docs/agents/siderian/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        &lt;h2 id=&#34;abilities&#34;&gt;Abilities&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;propaganda-propagandaimagespropagandapng&#34;&gt;Propaganda &lt;img src=&#34;/Rising-Constellation-FAQ/images/propaganda.PNG&#34; alt=&#34;Propaganda&#34;&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This ability is used to take control over an AI controlled system. It takes the agent&amp;rsquo;s propaganda skill and compares it to the current stability of the system. The attempt takes a long amount of time (~8 hours in legacy). Requires the agent to rest afterwards before they can use any other abilities.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;how-do-i-defend-against-it-other-than-high-stability&#34;&gt;How do I defend against it other than high stability?&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you notice the Siderian in your dominion and suspect a propaganda attempt, you can flip your dominion into a system, canceling the agent&amp;rsquo;s action.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;destabilize-destabilizeimagesdestabilizationpng&#34;&gt;Destabilize &lt;img src=&#34;/Rising-Constellation-FAQ/images/destabilization.PNG&#34; alt=&#34;Destabilize&#34;&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This ability reduces the stability of the current system. Useful for setting up a propaganda action later, or reducing the efficiency of the current system. Takes a moderate amount of time (~2.5 hours in legacy). Requires the agent to rest afterwards before they can use any other abilities.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;seduce-seduceimagesseductionpng&#34;&gt;Seduce &lt;img src=&#34;/Rising-Constellation-FAQ/images/seduction.PNG&#34; alt=&#34;Seduce&#34;&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This ability can only be used when in the same system as an enemy agent who is visible. This ability compares the siderian agent&amp;rsquo;s seduction skill against the target agent&amp;rsquo;s Determination &lt;img src=&#34;/Rising-Constellation-FAQ/images/agent_determination.png&#34; alt=&#34;Determination&#34;&gt;. If successful, will convert the agent to your side! Instantaneous. TODO/verify: Requires the agent to rest afterwards before they can use any other abilities.&lt;/p&gt;

      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Docs: Erased</title>
      <link>/Rising-Constellation-FAQ/docs/agents/erased/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/Rising-Constellation-FAQ/docs/agents/erased/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        &lt;h2 id=&#34;abilities&#34;&gt;Abilities&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;infiltration-infiltrationimagesinfiltrationpng&#34;&gt;Infiltration &lt;img src=&#34;/Rising-Constellation-FAQ/images/infiltration.PNG&#34; alt=&#34;Infiltration&#34;&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Infiltration takes somewhere between 2-3 hours and compares the erased agent&amp;rsquo;s infiltration skill against the system&amp;rsquo;s &lt;a href=&#34;/Rising-Constellation-FAQ/docs/concepts/_index.md#intelligence&#34;&gt;intelligence&lt;/a&gt; and if successful installs 1 malware, or 2 with a critical success, in the system, increasing visibility on the system, and contributing to the &lt;a href=&#34;/Rising-Constellation-FAQ/docs/concepts/victory/#path-of-shadows#&#34;&gt;Path of Shadow&lt;/a&gt; victory&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;how-can-i-remove-malware-in-a-system&#34;&gt;How can I remove malware in a system?&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;By increasing your &lt;a href=&#34;/Rising-Constellation-FAQ/docs/concepts/#what-exactly-does-cybersecurity-do-cybersecurityimagescybersecuritypng&#34;&gt;cybersecurity&lt;/a&gt; in the system&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;can-i-have-more-than-4-malware-in-a-system&#34;&gt;Can I have more than 4 malware in a system?&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Yes, won&amp;rsquo;t give shadow paths points but it will allow to keep the 5 visibility longer if cybersecurity kicks in&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;can-i-perform-infiltration-without-any-skill-points-on-my-erased&#34;&gt;Can I perform infiltration without any skill points on my erased?&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Yes, but with a lower likelihood of success&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;sabotage-sabotageimagessabotagepng&#34;&gt;Sabotage &lt;img src=&#34;/Rising-Constellation-FAQ/images/sabotage.PNG&#34; alt=&#34;Sabotage&#34;&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This ability allows erased agents to damage fleets. It compares the erased agent&amp;rsquo;s sabotage skill VS the protection &lt;img src=&#34;/Rising-Constellation-FAQ/images/agent_protection.png&#34; alt=&#34;protection&#34;&gt; skill of the navarch controlling the target fleet. Upon success it will damage ships randomly in the fleet. The action is instantaneous.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;removal-removalimagesremovalpng&#34;&gt;Removal &lt;img src=&#34;/Rising-Constellation-FAQ/images/removal.PNG&#34; alt=&#34;Removal&#34;&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This ability allows the erased agent to assassinate an enemy governor or agent in the same system. It compares the erased agent&amp;rsquo;s removal skill against the enemy agent&amp;rsquo;s protection &lt;img src=&#34;/Rising-Constellation-FAQ/images/agent_protection.png&#34; alt=&#34;protection&#34;&gt; skill. Upon success it will remove the agent. The action is instantaneous.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Note: When removing a navarch agent with a fleet, it will be replaced with a lv 1 navarch, and the fleet will remain intact&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;!-- 
This is a normal paragraph following a header. Knausgaard kale chips snackwave microdosing cronut copper mug swag synth bitters letterpress glossier **craft beer**. Mumblecore bushwick authentic gochujang vegan chambray meditation jean shorts irony. Viral farm-to-table kale chips, pork belly palo santo distillery activated charcoal aesthetic jianbing air plant woke lomo VHS organic. Tattooed locavore succulents heirloom, small batch sriracha echo park DIY af. Shaman you probably haven&#39;t heard of them copper mug, crucifix green juice vape *single-origin coffee* brunch actually. Mustache etsy vexillologist raclette authentic fam. Tousled beard humblebrag asymmetrical. I love turkey, I love my job, I love my friends, I love Chardonnay!

Deae legum paulatimque terra, non vos mutata tacet: dic. Vocant docuique me plumas fila quin afuerunt copia haec o neque.

On big screens, paragraphs and headings should not take up the full container width, but we want tables, code blocks and similar to take the full width.

Scenester tumeric pickled, authentic crucifix post-ironic fam freegan VHS pork belly 8-bit yuccie PBR&amp;B. **I love this life we live in**.


## Second Header 2

&gt; This is a blockquote following a header. Bacon ipsum dolor sit amet t-bone doner shank drumstick, pork belly porchetta chuck sausage brisket ham hock rump pig. Chuck kielbasa leberkas, pork bresaola ham hock filet mignon cow shoulder short ribs biltong.

### Header 3

```
This is a code block following a header.
```

Next level leggings before they sold out, PBR&amp;B church-key shaman echo park. Kale chips occupy godard whatever pop-up freegan pork belly selfies. Gastropub Belinda subway tile woke post-ironic seitan. Shabby chic man bun semiotics vape, chia messenger bag plaid cardigan. 

#### Header 4

* This is an unordered list following a header.
* This is an unordered list following a header.
* This is an unordered list following a header.

##### Header 5

1. This is an ordered list following a header.
2. This is an ordered list following a header.
3. This is an ordered list following a header.

###### Header 6

| What      | Follows         |
|-----------|-----------------|
| A table   | A header        |
| A table   | A header        |
| A table   | A header        |

----------------

There&#39;s a horizontal rule above and below this.

----------------

Here is an unordered list:

* Liverpool F.C.
* Chelsea F.C.
* Manchester United F.C.

And an ordered list:

1. Michael Brecker
2. Seamus Blake
3. Branford Marsalis

And an unordered task list:

- [x] Create a Hugo theme
- [x] Add task lists to it
- [ ] Take a vacation

And a &#34;mixed&#34; task list:

- [ ] Pack bags
- ?
- [ ] Travel!

And a nested list:

* Jackson 5
  * Michael
  * Tito
  * Jackie
  * Marlon
  * Jermaine
* TMNT
  * Leonardo
  * Michelangelo
  * Donatello
  * Raphael

Definition lists can be used with Markdown syntax. Definition headers are bold.

Name
: Godzilla

Born
: 1952

Birthplace
: Japan

Color
: Green


----------------

Tables should have bold headings and alternating shaded rows.

| Artist            | Album           | Year |
|-------------------|-----------------|------|
| Michael Jackson   | Thriller        | 1982 |
| Prince            | Purple Rain     | 1984 |
| Beastie Boys      | License to Ill  | 1986 |

If a table is too wide, it should scroll horizontally.

| Artist            | Album           | Year | Label       | Awards   | Songs     |
|-------------------|-----------------|------|-------------|----------|-----------|
| Michael Jackson   | Thriller        | 1982 | Epic Records | Grammy Award for Album of the Year, American Music Award for Favorite Pop/Rock Album, American Music Award for Favorite Soul/R&amp;B Album, Brit Award for Best Selling Album, Grammy Award for Best Engineered Album, Non-Classical | Wanna Be Startin&#39; Somethin&#39;, Baby Be Mine, The Girl Is Mine, Thriller, Beat It, Billie Jean, Human Nature, P.Y.T. (Pretty Young Thing), The Lady in My Life |
| Prince            | Purple Rain     | 1984 | Warner Brothers Records | Grammy Award for Best Score Soundtrack for Visual Media, American Music Award for Favorite Pop/Rock Album, American Music Award for Favorite Soul/R&amp;B Album, Brit Award for Best Soundtrack/Cast Recording, Grammy Award for Best Rock Performance by a Duo or Group with Vocal | Let&#39;s Go Crazy, Take Me With U, The Beautiful Ones, Computer Blue, Darling Nikki, When Doves Cry, I Would Die 4 U, Baby I&#39;m a Star, Purple Rain |
| Beastie Boys      | License to Ill  | 1986 | Mercury Records | noawardsbutthistablecelliswide | Rhymin &amp; Stealin, The New Style, She&#39;s Crafty, Posse in Effect, Slow Ride, Girls, (You Gotta) Fight for Your Right, No Sleep Till Brooklyn, Paul Revere, Hold It Now, Hit It, Brass Monkey, Slow and Low, Time to Get Ill |

----------------

Code snippets like `var foo = &#34;bar&#34;;` can be shown inline.

Also, `this should vertically align` ~~`with this`~~ ~~and this~~.

Code can also be shown in a block element.

```
foo := &#34;bar&#34;;
bar := &#34;foo&#34;;
```

Code can also use syntax highlighting.

```go
func main() {
  input := `var foo = &#34;bar&#34;;`

  lexer := lexers.Get(&#34;javascript&#34;)
  iterator, _ := lexer.Tokenise(nil, input)
  style := styles.Get(&#34;github&#34;)
  formatter := html.New(html.WithLineNumbers())

  var buff bytes.Buffer
  formatter.Format(&amp;buff, style, iterator)

  fmt.Println(buff.String())
}
```

```
Long, single-line code blocks should not wrap. They should horizontally scroll if they are too long. This line should be long enough to demonstrate this.
```

Inline code inside table cells should still be distinguishable.

| Language    | Code               |
|-------------|--------------------|
| Javascript  | `var foo = &#34;bar&#34;;` |
| Ruby        | `foo = &#34;bar&#34;{`      |

----------------

Small images should be shown at their actual size.

![](https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/thumb/9/9e/Picea_abies_shoot_with_buds%2C_Sogndal%2C_Norway.jpg/240px-Picea_abies_shoot_with_buds%2C_Sogndal%2C_Norway.jpg)

Large images should always scale down and fit in the content container.

![](https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/thumb/9/9e/Picea_abies_shoot_with_buds%2C_Sogndal%2C_Norway.jpg/1024px-Picea_abies_shoot_with_buds%2C_Sogndal%2C_Norway.jpg)

_The photo above of the Spruce Picea abies shoot with foliage buds: Bjørn Erik Pedersen, CC-BY-SA._


## Components

### Alerts



&lt;div class=&#34;alert alert-primary&#34; role=&#34;alert&#34;&gt;


    This is an alert.

&lt;/div&gt;



&lt;div class=&#34;alert alert-primary&#34; role=&#34;alert&#34;&gt;
&lt;h4 class=&#34;alert-heading&#34;&gt;Note&lt;/h4&gt;

    This is an alert with a title.

&lt;/div&gt;



&lt;div class=&#34;alert alert-primary&#34; role=&#34;alert&#34;&gt;
&lt;h4 class=&#34;alert-heading&#34;&gt;Note&lt;/h4&gt;

    This is an alert with a title and &lt;strong&gt;Markdown&lt;/strong&gt;.

&lt;/div&gt;



&lt;div class=&#34;alert alert-success&#34; role=&#34;alert&#34;&gt;


    This is a successful alert.

&lt;/div&gt;



&lt;div class=&#34;alert alert-warning&#34; role=&#34;alert&#34;&gt;


    This is a warning.

&lt;/div&gt;



&lt;div class=&#34;alert alert-warning&#34; role=&#34;alert&#34;&gt;
&lt;h4 class=&#34;alert-heading&#34;&gt;Warning&lt;/h4&gt;

    This is a warning with a title.

&lt;/div&gt;



## Another Heading

Add some sections here to see how the ToC looks like. Bacon ipsum dolor sit amet t-bone doner shank drumstick, pork belly porchetta chuck sausage brisket ham hock rump pig. Chuck kielbasa leberkas, pork bresaola ham hock filet mignon cow shoulder short ribs biltong.

### This Document

Inguina genus: Anaphen post: lingua violente voce suae meus aetate diversi. Orbis unam nec flammaeque status deam Silenum erat et a ferrea. Excitus rigidum ait: vestro et Herculis convicia: nitidae deseruit coniuge Proteaque adiciam *eripitur*? Sitim noceat signa *probat quidem*. Sua longis *fugatis* quidem genae.


### Pixel Count

Tilde photo booth wayfarers cliche lomo intelligentsia man braid kombucha vaporware farm-to-table mixtape portland. PBR&amp;B pickled cornhole ugh try-hard ethical subway tile. Fixie paleo intelligentsia pabst. Ennui waistcoat vinyl gochujang. Poutine salvia authentic affogato, chambray lumbersexual shabby chic.

### Contact Info

Plaid hell of cred microdosing, succulents tilde pour-over. Offal shabby chic 3 wolf moon blue bottle raw denim normcore poutine pork belly.


### External Links

Stumptown PBR&amp;B keytar plaid street art, forage XOXO pitchfork selvage affogato green juice listicle pickled everyday carry hashtag. Organic sustainable letterpress sartorial scenester intelligentsia swag bushwick. Put a bird on it stumptown neutra locavore. IPhone typewriter messenger bag narwhal. Ennui cold-pressed seitan flannel keytar, single-origin coffee adaptogen occupy yuccie williamsburg chillwave shoreditch forage waistcoat.



```
This is the final element on the page and there should be no margin below this.
``` --&gt;

      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Docs: Dominions and Autonomous Systems</title>
      <link>/Rising-Constellation-FAQ/docs/systems/dominions/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/Rising-Constellation-FAQ/docs/systems/dominions/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        &lt;h2 id=&#34;general&#34;&gt;General&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;do-ai-controlled-systems-build-their-own-buildings&#34;&gt;Do AI controlled systems build their own buildings?&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;They automatically construct buildings over time, very inefficiently. They stop building and upgrading when all of their build slots are full.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;how-do-i-gain-control-of-a-dominion-or-autonomous-system&#34;&gt;How do I gain control of a Dominion or Autonomous System?&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;People can flip them to their faction by 2 means:
use Siderians to destabilize and then propaganda them to flip them into dominions
&lt;em&gt;OR&lt;/em&gt;
Use a navarch with a fleet to conquer it as a system.
Both of these will require an open slot (either as dominion, or system slot)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;where-should-i-take-a-dominion&#34;&gt;Where should I take a Dominion?&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Anywhere where your faction could use an additional system controlled, or a system which you think would be valuable from a resource generation or population perspective. Releasing systems into Dominions is a good way to ensure they have good income and population, freeing up a system slot for a potentially more forward location.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;can-i-use-a-colony-ship-to-take-control-of-an-autonomous-system&#34;&gt;Can I use a colony ship to take control of an autonomous system?&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;No, only conquest or propaganda&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;what-sectors-can-i-take-over-an-ai-controlled-system-in&#34;&gt;What sectors can I take over an AI controlled system in?&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You can only take control of systems in sectors adjacent to one your faction already owns, or in a sector your faction owns.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;autonomous-systems&#34;&gt;Autonomous systems&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;are-they-farmable&#34;&gt;Are they farmable?&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;yes, Pillaging them is a good way to both level up your agents, and gain resources, repairing buildings is not too hard if someone takes it over. see &lt;a href=&#34;/Rising-Constellation-FAQ/docs/agents/navarch/#pillaging&#34;&gt;Pillaging&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;dominions&#34;&gt;Dominions&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;what-do-i-get-for-having-a-dominion&#34;&gt;What do I get for having a dominion?&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You get a base 30% of the resources (credit/technology/ideology) generated by the system, it counts towards ownership of sector for your faction, and its population counts towards the Path of Influence victory. You can view your current dominion tax rate in the overview panel (bottom left corner button), it can be increased with Lexes&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;if-i-queue-a-bunch-of-upgrades-in-a-system-and-then-flip-it-to-domain-does-it-continue-on-its-happy-path&#34;&gt;If I queue a bunch of upgrades in a system and then flip it to domain, does it continue on its happy path?&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;yes&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;if-i-develop-a-system-then-switch-it-over-to-a-domain-system-does-the-ai-then-re-build-everything-or-would-it-stay-optimized-to-what-i-have-created&#34;&gt;If I develop a system then switch it over to a domain system, does the AI then re-build everything or would it stay optimized to what I have created?&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;IA can&amp;rsquo;t destroy then rebuild, so it will stay optimized. However, it won&amp;rsquo;t upgrade them all the way (stops when all the slots are taken by a building)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Swapping a system from dominion to system has an increasing ideology cost of +5k each time you flip any system. It is sometimes better to abandon the system and then take control with a siderian, takes more time but has no increasing cost.&lt;/p&gt;

      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Docs: Buildings</title>
      <link>/Rising-Constellation-FAQ/docs/systems/buildings/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/Rising-Constellation-FAQ/docs/systems/buildings/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        &lt;h3 id=&#34;monolith---does-it-scale-based-on-planet-or-system-population&#34;&gt;Monolith - Does it scale based on planet or system population?&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It uses the entire system population, you can tell by the icon it uses: &lt;img src=&#34;/Rising-Constellation-FAQ/images/system_population.png&#34; alt=&#34;System Population&#34;&gt; rather than &lt;img src=&#34;/Rising-Constellation-FAQ/images/planet_population.PNG&#34; alt=&#34;Planet Population&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;buildings-costs&#34;&gt;Buildings Costs&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;table&gt;
&lt;thead&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;th&gt;Name&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th&gt;Building Location&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th&gt;Production cost by level &lt;br/&gt; Credit Cost by level&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/thead&gt;
&lt;tbody&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Swarm of Self-Drilling Machines&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Asteroid or Moon&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;300/1250/7500/15000/25000&lt;br/&gt;3900/8320/13520/19500/26000&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Refining Ducts&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Asteroid or Moon&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;120/2000/20000/44000/80000&lt;br/&gt;2000/6400/10400/15000/20000&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Experiment Station&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Asteroid or Moon&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;150/1000/10000/22000/40000&lt;br/&gt;6000/12800/20800/30000/40000&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Business Arch&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Asteroid or Moon&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;2500/10000/60000/120000/200000&lt;br/&gt;40000/40000/64000/104000/160000&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Orbital Terminus&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Asteroid or Moon&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;1600/6000/36000/72000/120000&lt;br/&gt;20000/32000/52000/75000/100000&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Constellation of Lures&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Asteroid or Moon&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;100/250/1500/3000/5000&lt;br/&gt;3750/8000/13000/18750/25000&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Zero-G-Arena&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Asteroid or Moon&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;800/3200/9600/25600/64000&lt;br/&gt;9900/21120/34320/49500/66000&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;O.P.U.&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Asteroid or Moon&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;200/1500/15000/33000/60000&lt;br/&gt;3300/7040/11440/16500/22000&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;S-01 Assembly Line&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Asteroid or Moon&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;400/1600/4800/12800/32000&lt;br/&gt;10500/17500/28000/45500/70000&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;S-02 Assembly Line&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Asteroid or Moon&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;800/3200/9600/25600/64000&lt;br/&gt;15000/25000/40000/65000/100000&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Space Dock&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Asteroid or Moon&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;1500/6000/18000/48000/120000&lt;br/&gt;40000/62500/100000/162500/250000&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Assembly Superstructure&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Asteroid or Moon&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;3000/12000/36000/96000/240000&lt;br/&gt;100000/107500/172000/279500/430000&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;S.L.S.D. Network&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Asteroid or Moon&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;360/1500/4500/12000/30000&lt;br/&gt;4950/10560/17160/24750/33000&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Megapolis&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Habitable&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;120/1000/6000/12000/20000&lt;br/&gt;8400/17920/29120/42000/56000&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Residential District&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Habitable&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;30/250/1500/3000/5000&lt;br/&gt;1950/4160/6760/9750/13000&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Hive Cities&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Habitable&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;300/1250/7500/15000/25000&lt;br/&gt;4500/9600/15600/22500/30000&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Residential Archipelago&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Habitable&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;450/3750/22500/45000/75000&lt;br/&gt;7500/16000/26000/37500/50000&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Industrial Hub&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Habitable&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;500/2750/27500/60500/110000&lt;br/&gt;6000/12800/20800/30000/40000&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Orbital Link&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Habitable&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;4000/8000/48000/96000/160000&lt;br/&gt;70000/112000/182000/262500/350000&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Delta Polytech&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Habitable&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;70/375/3750/8250/15000&lt;br/&gt;1500/3200/5200/7500/10000&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Accelerator&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Habitable&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;15000/43750/87500/175000/350000&lt;br/&gt;72000/90000/144000/234000/360000&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Citadel&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Habitable&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;120/500/5000/11000/20000&lt;br/&gt;1500/3200/5200/7500/10000&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Floating Gardens&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Habitable&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;1200/4850/14550/38800/97000&lt;br/&gt;15000/32000/52000/75000/100000&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Network of Artificial Islands&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Habitable&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;2200/9000/27000/72000/180000&lt;br/&gt;50000/62500/100000/162500/250000&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Commercial Artery&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Habitable&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;200/1500/15000/33000/60000&lt;br/&gt;4000/12800/20800/30000/40000&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Reflect District&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Habitable&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;20000/58125/116250/232500/465000&lt;br/&gt;140000/97500/156000/253500/390000&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Planetary Shield&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Habitable&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;1000/4000/12000/32000/80000&lt;br/&gt;11250/24000/39000/56250/75000&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Preserved Echosystem&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Habitable&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;12000/35000/70000/140000/280000&lt;br/&gt;64000/87000/130500/188500/290000&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Orb-Intel&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Habitable&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;7500/18750/37500/75000/150000&lt;br/&gt;18750/40000/65000/93750/125000&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Convention Center&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Habitable&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;10000/2250/22500/49500/90000&lt;br/&gt;4800/10240/16640/24000/32000&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Central Hub&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Sterile&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;130/1100/6600/13200/22000&lt;br/&gt;9000/19200/31200/45000/60000&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Array of Excavators&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Sterile&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;200/1000/6000/12000/20000&lt;br/&gt;1950/4160/6760/9750/13000&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Capsule Cities&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Sterile&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;200/1000/6000/12000/20000&lt;br/&gt;3450/7360/11960/17250/23000&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Metamaterials Factory&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Sterile&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;30000/60000/120000/240000/480000&lt;br/&gt;180000/150000/240000/390000/600000&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Space Elevator&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Sterile&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;1500/6000/18000/48000/120000&lt;br/&gt;22500/48000/78000/112500/150000&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Impact Research Station&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Sterile&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;250/1750/17500/38500/70000&lt;br/&gt;3750/8000/13000/18750/25000&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Holodome&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Sterile&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;2000/8100/24300/64800/162000&lt;br/&gt;3000/6400/10400/15000/20000&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Monolith&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Sterile&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;20000/58750/117500/235000/470000&lt;br/&gt;160000/105000/168000/273000/420000&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Omnimarket&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Sterile&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;150/1125/11250/24750/45000&lt;br/&gt;8000/16000/26000/37500/50000&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Industrial Spaceport&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Sterile&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;1400/5500/16500/44000/110000&lt;br/&gt;9000/19200/31200/45000/60000&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;C.N.D.&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Sterile&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;5000/15000/30000/60000/120000&lt;br/&gt;19500/41600/67600/97500/130000&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Interception Tunnels&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Sterile&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;800/3100/9300/24800/62000&lt;br/&gt;9750/20800/33800/48750/65000&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Hyperdrive Circuit&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Sterile&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;600/2400/7200/19200/48000&lt;br/&gt;20250/43200/70200/101250/135000&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Aerospace Military Academy&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Sterile&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;6000/17500/35000/70000/140000&lt;br/&gt;19500/41600/67600/97500/130000&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Integrated Proxy Systems&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Sterile&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;250/1875/18750/41250/75000&lt;br/&gt;4050/8640/14040/20250/27000&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;

      </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
