<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Unofficial Rising Constellation FAQ – Placeholders</title>
    <link>/categories/placeholders/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Placeholders on Unofficial Rising Constellation FAQ</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    
	  <atom:link href="/categories/placeholders/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
      
        
      
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Docs: Systems</title>
      <link>/docs/systems/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/docs/systems/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        &lt;h3 id=&#34;prodction&#34;&gt;Prodction&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;most-of-my-time-so-far-is-spent-waiting-for-science-and-ideology-points-my-production-is-not-working-should-i-be-using-it-for-something&#34;&gt;Most of my time so far is spent waiting for science and ideology points. My production is not working, should I be using it for something?&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;it&amp;rsquo;s completely normal that the first 2 days you are not capping your production and are waiting on techno and ideo, don&amp;rsquo;t worry.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;what-is-the-difference-between-mobilized-and-populations&#34;&gt;What is the difference between mobilized and populations?&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If there are more number of jobs available than population, there is a penalty
Each building will say how many mobilized workers it requires. For example requires 2 workers to function optimally, the tooltip on the population icon shows how many your buildings require, vs the total number of people in your system, if the mobilized value is greater than the total you will see penalties in your resource production
TODO images&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;system-population&#34;&gt;System Population&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;How do populations within a system balance between planets?
does it every time you have a new pop it tries to even it between all the planets&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;colonizing&#34;&gt;Colonizing&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;if-i-am-going-to-colonize-does-it-matter-how-far-it-is-from-my-home-world&#34;&gt;If I am going to colonize, does it matter how far it is from my home world?&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;where to colonize : in early game, to get your second system, it is advised to get one near you to start building on it faster. But after that, it always depends on the systems available, the faction strategy,etc&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;can-i-reserve-a-system&#34;&gt;Can I reserve a system?&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Each faction usually has a chat room dedicated to system reservation to avoid multiple people sending colony ships to the same system and wasting time. Pick a system that looks good to you, and put the NAME XXX:YYY coordinates in the room (these can be found by clicking on the system,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;what-sectors-can-i-colonize-a-system-in&#34;&gt;What sectors can I colonize a system in?&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You can only take control of systems in sectors adjacent to one your faction already owns, or in a sector your faction owns.&lt;/p&gt;

      </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
